Meyers, W.B. Papers 5630
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
W.B. Meyers Papers
1963-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Meyers, W.B.
5630
18 cubic feet
18 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Reading files, agreements, resolutions, election minutes, constitution reports, Congressional records, semi-annual reports and employee exhibits
5677098
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 26, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Biographical / Historical
W.B. Meyers was an officer in the Switchmen's Union of North America.
Biographical / Historical
The Switchmen's Union of North America is among the older of the railway brotherhoods. Beginning in 1877 with the formation of a local Switchmen's organization in Chicago, the movement became national when the Switchmen's Mutual Aid Association of North America held its first meeting nine years later.
This association was destroyed, as a result of a disastrous lockout by the Chicago Northwestern and the 1888 strike against the Chicago, Burlington and Quincy which had equally unfortunate results. Building on what was left of the S.M.A.A., several lodges met in Kansas City in October of 1854 and formed the Switchmen's Union of North America.
By the time of its merger into the United Transportation Union in 1969, the single Chicago labor organization of 1877 had grown to international status with 275 lodges in the United States and Canada having a combined membership of 12,000.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5034: Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5034 MB: Switchmen's Union of North America Memorabilia 5034 P: Switchmen's Union of North America Photographs 5084: Switchmen's Union of North America Additional Records 5405 mf: Switchmen's Union of North America Constitutions on Microfilm 5406 mf: Switchmen's Union of North America Arbitration on Microfilm 5447: Switchmen's Union of North America Additional Unification Minutes and Convention Proceedings 5556: Switchmen's Union of North America Additional Records 5556 AV: Switchmen's Union of North America Audio-Visual Materials 5590: Switchmen's Union of North America Lake Shore Lodge 55 Membership Registers 5613: Switchmen's Union of North America Oakland Lodge 158 Meeting Minutes
Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Meyers, William Roy.; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Burlington Northern Inc.; Switchmen's Union of North America; United Transportation Union
5677098
- Calendars. (Box 1)
  - NP Speirs Reading Copies, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    January 1969 thru June 1969
  - N P Speirs Reading Copies, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    July 1,1969-
  - W.R. Meyers Reading file, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    March 18,1969 to September 30,1969
  - WR Meyers Reading File October 1,1969 to December 31,1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - WR Meyers Reading File, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    January 1,1970 to June 14, 1970
  - WR Meyers Reading File (Box 1, Folder 6)
    June 15, 1970 to December 31,1970
  - WR Meyers Reading File, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    January 1,1971 to June 30, 1971
  - WR Meyers Reading File (Box 1, Folder 8)
    January 1,1972 to June 30,1972
  - DW Collins Reading File, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    March 1, 1972 - June 30, 1972
  - WR Meyers Reading File, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    July 1, 1972 - December 21, 1972
  - WR Meyers Reading File (Box 1, Folder 11)
    July 1, 1971 to December 31, 1971
  - N P Speirs Reading File (Box 1, Folder 12)
    January 1,1973 to June 30, 1973
- Correspondence: A-Football. (Box 2)
  - Article XX AFL-CIO Jurisdiction (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Assemblyman Race 1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Attained Age - Membership (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Beneficiary Membership, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - BLE Agreement, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    March 10,1969
  - Board of Education (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bowser (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bowser (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Convention - UTU, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - UTU Convention, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - UTU National Convention, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Counter Proposals, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    November 1, 1959
  - 1966 Crew Consist Issue (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Dissent Award - PLB #A67 UTU(s) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Dissent Award #1 PLB #467 UTU(s) Research Material (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Effects of 282 Court (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Board #130 Non-Ops, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Board #121 - SUNA - 1960 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Emergency Board #172 BRT v. I.C. - L&N - Crew Consist (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Extra Man - Holiday (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Alleged Featherbedding (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Finance and Insurance Work Dec. 1956 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - F&I Board Work Dec 1955 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - F&I Work May June 1959 - Convention (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - F&I Board Work Dec. 1958 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - F&I Board Work June 1958 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - F&I Board Work Dec. 1957 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Minutes F&I Board (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Emergency Board 177 - Fireman's Manning Issue (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Football 1956 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Football 1957 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Football 1958 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Football 1953 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Football 1952 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Football 1950 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Correspondence: Freedom - I. (Box 3)
  - Freedom Train (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Gen. Chm. Association (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Gen. Committee (S)(GN) B.N. George J. Kelley 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Glover (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Health and Welfare - Section Six Notice Nov. 1,1967 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - H/W (SUNA) 1967-8 Carriers, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - H/W 1971-2 Notice (Box 3, Folder 7)
    October 15,1971
  - H/W 1973-4 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - H/W Negotiations 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Insurance Committee Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ins. Committee 1951 Membership (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Membership 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Insurance Committee Reports (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Insurance Com Work Jan. 1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Insurance Committee Work Convention, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Insurance Work 1947 After Convention (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Insurance Committee Work May 1948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Insurance Committee Work May 1949 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Insurance Committee Work May, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Insurance Committee Work 1951 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Ins. Convention Work, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Insurance and Finance Committee Work June 1952 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Insurance Committee Work June 1956 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Insurance Committee Work June 1957 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Insurance - UTU (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Correspondence: K-Rook. (Box 4)
  - Kurtz (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Labor Attach (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Legal Aid Committee #107 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Lodge #107 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lonn, Lloyd E. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Machinist Airline Strike 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - WR Meyers First Division SUNA (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - WR Meyers (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Promulgated Rules Dispute WR Meyers (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Non-Op Insurance (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - NP System Vote (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Organizing NYC (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Poland, C.E. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Politics (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Procedural Question B&O (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - RRA Supplemental Pension (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Rail Pax (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - RR Work Rule Demands 1959 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Regular Man- Holiday (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Renumbered Locals (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Rook, David (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Correspondence: Rules-SUKA Convention. (Box 5)
  - Rules Movement 1958 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Rules Movement 1960-1961 Study Commission (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Rules 1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Board #154 Rules (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Shop Craft Strike 1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Shop Crafts Wage Movement - Emergency Board #176, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Neil P. Speirs (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - SUNA Agreement, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - SUNA Agreement, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    April 10, 1967
  - SU Retirement Resolution (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - SUNA Convention 1951 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Special Convention SUNA, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    April 1953
  - 1955 SUNA Convention Work Etc. Minute Elections (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 1955 Convention SUNA Constitution Work (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - S.U. Convention 1955 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1959 Convention (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - SUNA Gen. Chm Meeting, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Jan. 20-21, 1966
  - 1963 SUNA Convention (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 1967 SUNA Convention (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Correspondence: SUNA Membership - Z. (Box 6)
  - SUNA Membership 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - SUNA Sec. Treasury Local Reports (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - SUNA Wage & Rules 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - SUNA Wage Movement 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Superior Federation of Labor (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Supplemental Pensions, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Tentative Proposals (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - UTU Agreement March 19, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - UTU Agreement - April 15,1969 Engineers (Box 6, Folder 9)
    April 15,1969
  - Vacation (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Vriesacker (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Wage Agreement Conferences July 18-21, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Wage Negotiation, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Signed July 29,1968
  - Wage Proposal, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    July-Aug-1962
  - Wage and Rules 1973 Notice (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Wiley, Senator (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Wis. State Fed. Of Labor 1950 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Railroads, alphabetical. (Box 7)
  - Rules Movement 1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Rules Movement 1960-1961 Study Commission (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Rules 1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Board #154 Rules (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Shopcraft Strike 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Shop Crafts Wage Movement 1969-1970 Emergency Board 3176 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Neil P. Speirs (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - SUNA Agreement April 10,1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - SUNA Agreement, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    July 29, 1968
  - SUNA Convention 1951 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Special Convention SUNA April 1953 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1955 SUNA Convention Work Etc. Minute Elections (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1955 Convention SUNA Constitution Work (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - SU Convention 1955 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1959 Convention (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - SUNA Gen. Chm Meeting, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Jan 20-21, 1966
  - 1963 SUNA Convention (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - SUNA Convention 1967 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Railroads, alphabetical. (Box 8)
  - Current Developments Section (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - UTU - Trans. Conference (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Switchmen's Union Conventions, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Memorandum for Insurers, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Switchmen Union's Conventions, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Committee of Constitutions Reports (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Statistical Supplement (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Railroad Retirement Board (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - United Transportation Union (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Awards. (Box 9)
  - Docket 41596 O'Trembiak's Case C-4095, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - O'Trembiak 41596 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - O'Trembiak's Hearing Milw Rd (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Reinstatement Case James O'Trembiak - Milw Rd. - Chi. Term 41596 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - PLBA 399 B&O (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - PLB #399 Employees' Reply Submission To Carrier's Rebuttal Statement (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Awards. (Box 10)
  - Memorandum of Understanding - Burlington Northern Inc., and UTU (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Carrier's Submission - UTU v. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Carrier's Submission - UTU v. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Carrier's Submission - UTU v. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - UTU v. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific RR Co. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - UTU v. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - UTU and Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - UTU v. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - UTU v. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - UTU vs. Minneapolis, Northfield and Southern Railway Company (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - UTU v. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - UTU v. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - UTU v. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Awards. (Box 11)
  - UTU, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Switchmen's Union of North America vs. Portland Terminal Railroad Company (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Portland Terminal Railroad Company Agreements, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Articles VII and XIII, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    January 15, 1973
  - Articles V+VI (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Articles 1-4 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Articles VIII & IX (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - UTU and Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - UTU - General Committee (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - UTU v. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - UTU vs. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - UTU vs. Burlington Northern Inc. - Carrier's Submission (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - UTU vs. Burlington Northern Inc. 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Carrier's Submission - UTU v. Burlington Northern Inc. (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Awards. (Box 12)
  - Switchmen's Union of North America, AFL-CIO International Union (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Awards (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - UTU and B&O Carrier's Submission (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - UTU and Duluth Missabe and Iron Range Railway (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - UTU and Monon Railroad- Statement of Claim (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Nat'l Railroad Adjustment Board - Exhibits (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Employees Exhibits (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - UTU vs. Burlington Northern Inc. Award no. 1 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Agreement - UTU and Baltimore and Ohio Railroad (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - UTU Trainmen and Baltimore and Ohio Railroad (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the National Mediation Board - Emergency. Board No. 154 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Combination of Road and Yard Service (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Awards. (Box 13)
  - UTU-Wage Rules, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    December 16, 1971
  - UTU-Wages, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    May 26, 1970
  - Mediation Agreement, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Memorandum for the Record, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    April 16, 1970
  - Current Developments Section (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Record - Daily Digest, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    February 3, 1971
  - Congressional Record - Daily Digest, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Record, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    June 14, 1967
  - Congressional Record, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    April 8, 1970
  - UTU- Wage Rules Dispute (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - UTU - Back Pay, Fired, Resigned Employees (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - UTU - Wage Rules Dispute (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Emergency Board 178, Report (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Back Pay (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Mediation Agreement, Case A, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Jan. 27, 1972
- Awards. (Box 14)
  - Nat. Railroad Adjustment Board-Awards (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - UTU- Employees' Exhibits (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - UTU-Employees' Exhibits (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Operating Railroad Brotherhood Meetings-Minutes, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Minutes of Meetings of Organizations (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Mediation Agreement (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Agreements (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Agreements (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Switchmen's Union of North America (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Report, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Memorandum (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Switchmen's Union of North America (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Agreements- Wages, Rules (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - National Mediation Board (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - PLB #2305 UTUv.BN (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - PLB#467 Awards UTU v. M/W (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Otrembiak's Submission PLB #467 A#1 Milw Rd. (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Awards. (Box 15)
  - Award of Arbitration Board 282 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Employee's Reply to Carrier's Ex Parte Submission (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Employees' Exhibits PLB No. 837 UTU(s) v. IU Rwy. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Employees' Exhibits PLB No. 837 UTU(s) v. IU Rwy. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Employees' Reply to Carrier's Ex Parte Submission (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Employees' Exhibits PLB No. 837 UTU(s) v. IU Rwy. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Employees' Exhibits PLB No. 837 UTU(s) v. Rwy. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Employees' Reply to Carrier's Ex Parte Submission (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Employees' Exhibits PLB No. 837 UTU(s) IU Rwy. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Public Law Board No. 399 United Transportation Union (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Employees' Reply to Carrier's Ex Parte Submission (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Annual Reports. (Box 16)
  - PRC (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Laws Relating to Interstate Commerce and Transportation (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Railroad Retirement Board - 1973 Annual Report (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Seidenberg - The Labor Injunction In New York City (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Shop Craft 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Railway Labor Act, National Mediation Board 1934-1970 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Railroad Retirement Board - Annual Report 1970 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Railroad Retirement Board - Annual Report 1970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Volume 4 - Determination of Craft or Class (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Right of Way UTU-CBRT & GW - BRASC (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Senate - Railroad Shopcraft Dispute - 1967 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - The Interstate Commerce Act-Revised to October 1,1958 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Growth of Labor Law in the United States (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Railroad Work Rules Dispute, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Railroad Retirement Board Annual Report 1973 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Railroad Retirement Board 1972 Annual Report (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Railroad Retirement Board 1971 Annual Report (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Railroad Labor Dispute - 1967 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - SUNA 1963 Convention (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Railroad Retirement Board - Annual Report 1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Binders: annual, semi-annual and quarterly reports, minutes of meetings, contract agreements, manuals of investigation, collections of letters, merger report. (Box 17)
  - Great Northern: Northern Pacific CB&Q & SP&S Merger (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Hewitt's Index Digest of Important Decisions and Principles of the National Railroad Adjustment Board (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - W.R. Meyers (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Investigations - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Semi-Annual Report - UTU, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Semi-Annual Report - UTU, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Semi-Annual Report - UTU, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Semi-Annual Report - UTU, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Semi-Annual Report - UTU, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Semi-Annual Report - General Adjustment Committee, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - General Committee DRGW (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Semi-Annual Report SUNA DRGW (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - UTU DRGW (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - General Committee-Switchmen(D&RGW Railroad) United Transportation Union (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - United Transportation union - Burlington Northern General Committee (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - United Transportation Union - Burlington Northern General Committee (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - United Transportation Union - Burlington Northern General Committee (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - United Transportation Union - Burlington Northern General Committee - Quarterly Report (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Six Months Report - General Adjustment Committee, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    January 1,1970 to July 1, 1970
  - Six Months Report - General Adjustment Committee - UTU, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    July 1,1972 to January 1,1973
  - General Committee of Adjustment - Great Northern Railroad Company (Box 17, Folder 21)
- file folders - miscellaneous. (Box 18)
  - Washington State Legislative Board (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - New York Legislative Board (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Maine (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Signalmen's Strike (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Wisconsin Safe Crew Law (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Iowa Legislative Reports (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Minnesota Legislative Reports (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Burlington Northern (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania Legislative Reports (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - W.P. Cutter, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - WP Committee (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Merger GN-NP-CB&Q (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Northern Lines Merger ICC (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Clerks Agreement Northern Lines Merger (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - SUNA Health and Welfare, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 15)